Nobody tells you this when you first start dirt biking.
刚开始玩越野摩托时，没人会告诉你这件事。
The hard part is not about learning how to ride,
难的部分不是学会怎么骑车，
it's actually finding somebody who gets it.
其实是找到一个懂这件事的人。
My first real ride was brutal, it was 100 degrees outside, I was sweating through everything, my legs were shaking, my hands were tired, and honestly I could barely stay on the bike.
我第一次真正的骑行非常残酷，外面37度，我浑身都被汗湿透了，腿在发抖，手也没了力气，说实话我几乎坐不住车了。
But you know what the crazy thing is, I couldn't stop thinking about it.
但你知道疯狂的是什么吗，我一直忍不住想着它。
That's when I realized dirt biking is addictive.
那时我意识到，越野摩托会让人上瘾。
And it gets even better when you have somebody to share it to.
而当你有人可以分享时，它会变得更好。
However, most of what I found online felt scattered, outdated, or just not the way I wanted to be built.
然而，我在网上找到的大部分都感觉零散、过时，或者根本不是我想要的那种做法。
So as a software engineer, I set out to do the one thing I know how. To build DirtBikeX
所以作为一名软件工程师，我决定去做我唯一会做的事。去打造 DirtBikeX
myself. The kind of place I wish existed. It's got no bloat. You don't have to post
自己动手。我一直希望存在的那种地方。它没有臃肿的功能。你不用把同一个内容
the same thing twice. 21 languages. All the good stuff.
发两遍。21种语言。所有好东西都有。
Most importantly, a real chance for us to be seen by fellow riders, so if you've been looking
最重要的是，我们真正有机会被同好骑手看见，所以如果你也像我一样，一直在寻找
for dirt bike people like me, go and check out the invite code in the description. My name is Rubio
越野摩托伙伴，就去看看简介里的邀请码。我叫鲁比奥
and I'll be waiting for you there!
我在那里等你！